http://www.protica.com/privacypolicy.htm

Protica Research Corporation Internet Privacy Statement
Protica Research Corporation (Protica) is concerned for the privacy of its visitors to Protica web sites. The following statement generally describes the types of information collected at Protica's sites and the uses made of it.
Personally Identifiable Information
Protica Research Corporation collects personally identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or other information only when it is voluntarily submitted to us on this site. The portion of such information where you may describe for purposes of placing an order is held and processed under secure conditions at Protica (or at an agent of Protica) with access limited to appropriate Protica staff or other authorized agents having a requirement to maintain the confidentiality of the information. Protica uses or discloses personally identified information only with the visitor's consent or other legal authorization. The intended uses of the information are provided at the site where the information is collected. We may use the information to improve the content of our web site. We will not sell or rent personally identifiable information to any third party for that party's marketing purposes.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Protica Research Corporation also collects aggregate or non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to track data such as the total number of visits to our web sites, the number of visitors to each page of our web sites, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. We use this information, which remains in aggregate form, to understand how our visitors use our web sites so that we may make them better. We may also share this information with our partners or other outside companies. NO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS DISCLOSED IN THIS PROCESS.
Links to Other Web Sites
Protica Research Corporation web sites may provide links to other web sites as a service to our viewers. We believe these web sites provide helpful information. However, Protica does not endorse and is not responsible for the content of third-party sites. Nor does Protica have any control over the information you may choose to provide to these sites.
The privacy policy described here does not apply to those sites.
Children
Protica sites are directed at general audiences, not children. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 18 years of age.
Changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be communicated promptly on this page.
About Us|Our Product|Product Usage|Place Order|R&D|Q&A
Sitemap|Search|Help|Contact|Privacy Policy|Terms
Referral and Affiliate Program|Online Store|My Account
Home|Protica Publications|External Links
Copyright© 2001-2011 Protica, Inc.
The Food and Drug Administration has not evaluated the statements within this site. Our products are not intended to diagnose, treat, prevent, or cure any disease and are not intended for use as a weight loss supplement.
Seek a doctor's advice before beginning any weight loss or exercise program.
